Diego Arturo Quevedo Ramírez

Full Stack Developer

Azuqueca de Henares, Guadalajara (España), 19200

Tel: (34) 623 996 663

Mail: quevedodiego3008@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/DiegoQuevedo38

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/diego-arturo-quevedo-ramirez-2bb197281

About me

Full Stack Developer with a background focused on customer service, specialized in Back-End. Proficient in agile methodologies, GIT, Unit testing, data structures, algorithms, Regex, CSS and Back-End frameworks, Sequelize. Experience in developing Front End and Back End on multiple projects, both individual and group, using technologies such as TypeScript, JavaScript, React, Redux, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, and Node.Js.

Projects

Web Developer- Team Lead - "Rentify - Rent a hotel"

19/02/2024-15/03/2024, Academic experience HENRY Labs

Development of a functional Marketplace-style website for creating and booking hotels around the world, I was also in charge of the team management, assigning tasks and checking on updates, as well as posting every issue and communicating with the team. The used technologies were:

- Front: TypeScript, React, Redux, CSS, HTML, Cloudinary
- Back: TypeScript, JavaScript, Node.Js, Express.Js, Mocha, Dotenv
- Database: MongoDB, Mongoose, Firebase

Link of the repository: https://github.com/jlcarrascof/PF-Henry-Project Link of Vimeo: https://vimeo.com/924729366?share=copy

Full Stack Web Developer - "Pokemon SPA"

15/01/2024-02/02/ 2024, Academic experience HENRY Labs

Creation of a Single Page App based on Pokémon using an API with information from the Emerald edition. Technologies used:

- Front: JavaScript, React, Redux, CSS, HTML, Jest
- Back: Node.Js, Express.Js, Mocha, Dotenv
- Database: PostgreSQL y Sequelize

Link of the repository: https://github.com/DiegoQuevedo38/PI-Pokemon

Experience

InTouch CX, Sourcing-Recruiter

MAY 2022-JULY 2023, BOGOTÁ DC

Bilingual recruiter role sourcing and managing candidates interested in the company. Responsibilities included analyzing, selecting, interviewing, and processing hundreds of bilingual voice representative candidates, ensuring attention to detail and efficiency in team collaboration.

Teleperformance SAS, Customer Service Representative

AUGUST 2021-FEBRUARY 2022, BOGOTÁ DC

Bilingual customer service and technical support representative for Disney+/Star+ campaign, handling inquiries, technical issues, billing problems, and subscription guidance across the Americas.

Education

HENRY, Full Stack web Development 800 hours Theoretical-Practical, 2023

Intensive live bootcamp covering multiple programming languages such as JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Redux, SQL, Node, Express, Sequelize, among others. Applied knowledge in individual and group projects emphasizing teamwork and Agile Scrum methodologies.

Technologies

- Programming Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, MongoDB, SQL, Python, Git
- Framework Tools: React, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Node.Js, Express.Js, Mocha, Jest, Tailwind CSS, LESS, Dotenv, Mongoose, Angular
- Databases: MongoDB, Mongoose, Sequelize, PostgreSQL, Firebase, SQL Shell, PG Admin.
- Tools: GitHub, Railway, LucidChart, Slack, Postman, Vercel, Vimeo
- Agile: Scrum

Skills

- Teamwork
- Team management and Leadership
- Agile Mindset
- Proactivity and Adaptability
- Assertive Communication

Languages

Spanish | Native levelEnglish | C2/AdvancedGerman | A1/Basic